One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
Miras alınan irade,...
the tides of time, and humanity's dreams...
zamanın gelgitleri ve insanların hayalleri...
They cannot be stopped.
Bunların önüne geçilemez.
As long as people seek freedom,
İnsanlar, özgürlüğün anlamını aradığı sürece...
these things will never cease to be.
bunlar hep var olacak.
I only believe in the future -- I don't care if anyone laughs
Sadece geleceğe inanırım, gülen gülsün, aldırmam pek
That racing passion makes you shine
Bu yarış tutkusu seni öne çıkarır hep
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
Çok parlak ama yine de bakmak istiyorum
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
Bir yerlerde "estetiği" hissediyorum
I follow, follow in the footsteps
İzindeyim, hiçbir şeye benzemeyen
of a dream that resembles no one
bir hayalin izindeyim, yeniden
Until I dramatically get it
Ta ki dramatik bir anla ulaşana dek,
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
Görülmeyen bu hayalin peşine düşeceğim,
of a dream no one can see
onu yakalayıp gerçeğe dönüştüreceğim.
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
Seninle gideceğim, bu tutkuyla yanacağım
I don't really need everything to add up
Her şeyin mantıklı olmasına gerek yok zaten
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
Sıradan bir hayatı bırakıp
run for paradise instead
CENNETE koş hemen,
Foul Play
Kural İhlali
Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ah, ah, ah...
It's horrible! A dinosaur ate Nami!
Felaket! Nami’yi bir dinozor yedi!
Wait! What?!
Cidden mi?!
One moment we were running away from it,
Bir dinozordan kaçmak için...
and the next she had suddenly disappeared into the jungle!
ormana doğru birlikte koştuğumuz sırada aniden kayboldu!!
What have I done?!
Ben ne yaptım?!
I let my crewmate get killed!
Arkadaşımın ölmesine izin verdim!
H-Hold on!
D-Durun biraz!
Calm down, you two!
İkiniz de sakin olun!
– Huh?
– Ha?
You said she suddenly disappeared, but did you check and make sure?
Aniden yok oldu dedin, yani ona ne olduğunu görmedin değil mi?
Are you crazy?!
Kafayı mı yedin?!
I was too terrified to check and make sure!
O kadar korktum ki gidip bakamadım bile!
It was either a dinosaur or a beast!
Ya dinozor ya da canavardı!
What else could it have been?!
Başka ne olabilir?!
I don't know.
Bilemiyorum.
But if someone from Baroque Works followed us here,
Ama Baroque Works bizi bu adaya kadar takip etmiş olabilir.
then it would make sense if Nami was taken instead of you.
Sana kıyasla Nami-san'ın hedef alınması gayet doğal.
What?!
Ne?!
Baroque Works is on the island?!
Baroque Works bu adada mı?!
Wait...
Bekle...
why wouldn't they go after me?
Niye ben hedef alınmıyorum ki?
Because there's only a slim chance you're on their hit list.
Büyük ihtimalle Baroque Works'ün ölüm listesinde olmadığın için.
Makes sense!
Anladım!
Plus, we were probably supposed to drink that alcohol too!
O içki de bizim için hazırlanmış olabilir.
Alcohol?!
İçki mi?!
What alcohol?!
Ne içkisi?!
Brogy brought your alcohol to Dorry,
Brogy içkisini Dorry'ye verdi.
and when Dorry drank it, it exploded inside his stomach.
Dorry de içkiyi yudumladı, ardından içki midesinde patladı.
What?! Our alcohol exploded inside his stomach?!
Ne?! İçkimiz midesinde mi patladı?!
You're saying he continued the duel all busted up like that?!
O hâliyle düelloya mı gitti?!
And when I tried to stop him, this is what he did to me.
Onu durdurmaya çalıştım ama hâlimi görüyorsun.
You can't be serious!
Ciddi olamazsın!
Those two have fought on equal ground for 100 years with all their might!
Eşit şartlarda, var güçleriyle 100 yıldır dövüşüyorlar!
It's gotta be the most honorable battle ever fought in this world!
Bu, dünyanın gördüğü en asil dövüş olsa gerek!
Yeah...
Evet.
They can't settle the fight like this now!
Düello böyle bitmemeli!
What's wrong?!
Sorun nedir?!
He's still fighting.
Hâlâ dövüşüyorlar.
Yes. Dorry the Blue Ogre is quite stubborn indeed.
Evet. Mavi Dev Dorry epey inatçı biri.
Perhaps I should lend a hand.
Belki de bir el atmalıyım.
One century...
Tam bir asır sürdü.
It was a long battle!
Gerçekten uzun bir dövüştü!
Heaven has censured me.
İlahi adalet cezamı kesti.
Elbaph, the god of war, has decided my fate.
Savaş tanrısı Elbaf, kaderime hükmetti.
I didn't have his divine protection.
Onun ilahi korumasını yitirdim.
That is all.
Hepsi bu.
Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy?!
Luffy-san?!
Who was it?!
Kimdi o?!
Show yourself!
Çık ortaya!
Huh?
Ha?
Mr. 3, I think I heard something.
Bay 3, sanırım bir şey duydum.
How amusing!
Çok zevkli!
An underdog also-ran, yelping out here in the jungle!
Belki de ormandaki acınası bir eziğin ağlayışıydı!
Seventy-three... thousand...
Yetmiş üç... bin...
four hundred... sixty-seven duels.
dört yüz... altmış yedi düello.
four hundred sixty-six draws...
Yetmiş üç... bin... dört yüz altmış altı beraberlik...
and one win!
ve bir galibiyet!
Tears of joy over your victory?
Gözyaşların zafer sevincinden mi?
Simpletons have it so easy.
Cahillik mutluluktur.
Though, I suppose congratulations are in order.
Yine de tebrik etmek yerinde olur.
Tears of joy?!
Sevinç gözyaşları mı?!
What would you know?!
Sen ne anlarsın ki?!
Just who are you?!
Kimsin lan sen?!
Mr. 3.
Bay 3.
Please excuse the code name. I'm a mere formative artist.
Kod adımı kullandığım için üzgünüm. Ben yalnızca bir heykeltıraşım.
And this is my assistant and realist painter, Miss Golden Week.
Bu da yardımcım, realizm akımının ressamı Bayan Golden Week.
What's more, I've already captured you.
Dahası, seni çoktan yakaladım.
Wh-What is this?!
B-Bu da ne?!
Alright, Luffy!
Tamam, Luffy!
I dunno who we're dealing with, but I'll go take care of them myself!
Kim olduklarını bilmiyorum ama onları kendim haklayacağım!
I'll come with you!
Ben de geliyorum!
Yes! If you insist! I wouldn't mind the backup!
Peki! Madem ısrar ediyorsun! Desteğe hayır demem!
There's no need for that!
Buna gerek yok!
You guys again!
Demek sizdiniz!
You can have him back.
Onu geri alabilirsin.
We don't need him.
İhtiyacımız kalmadı.
Karoo!
Karoo!
Why, you...!
Ulan...!
Hey, who are they?
Hey. Onlar da kim?
They're from that last town!
Son uğradığımız kasabadaydılar!
What are you doing here?!
Ne yapıyorsunuz siz?!
Karoo has nothing to do with this!
Karoo'nun bununla bir ilgisi yok!
That's right. The bird has absolutely nothing to do with this.
Haklısın. O kuşun bununla kesinlikle bir ilgisi yok.
The only one we considered a threat was that straw hat guy.
Ama o hasır şapkalı adamın ciddi bir tehdit olabileceğini düşündük.
The plan was to make the bird squawk to lure you away from him,
Planımız, kuşu bağırtıp seni ondan uzaklaştırmaktı...
but that is one obstinate duck.
ama o epey inatçı bir ördek çıktı.
Now, then! Call for your owner!
Şimdi! Sahibini çağır!
Quack especially loud, and we'll let you go free!
Güçlü vakla ki özgür kalabilesin!
Fine! Want us to make you quack?!
Çok yazık! Zorla biz vaklatacağız!
Call for the princess!
Prensesi çağır.
Call for help...
Onu...
this instant!
hemen çağırsan iyi olur!
Open your mouth, you damn bird!
Aç gaganı, lanet olası kuş!
But it looks like Straw Hat's already out of the picture.
Ama görünen o ki Hasır Şapka çoktan saf dışı kalmış.
So the duck's no use to us now.
Bu yüzden artık kuşa ihtiyacımız yok.
Karoo...
Karoo...
What a stupid bird!
Ne aptal bir kuş!
Why, you...!
Adiler...!
Are you the ones who made the alcohol explode?!
Patlayan içki sizin işiniz miydi?!
Yes, that was us, but who are you?
Ah, evet. Sen de kimsin?
Is he on the list?
Listede miydi?
No, but he seems to be a shipmate. Let's make him disappear too!
Hayır ama belli ki onlardan biri. Onu da yok edelim.
So, you interfered with the giants' duel!
Demek devlerin düellosunu sabote eden sizdiniz.
It was them?!
Onlar mı yapmış?!
I'll kick their asses!
Canlarına okuyacağım!
You're the ones who'll disappear!
Yok edilecek olanlar sizlersiniz!
Oh? You're gonna start something, Miss Wednesday?
Oh? Bizi kendin mi karşılayacaksın, Bayan Wednesday?
What makes you think you're a match for officer agents?
İki rütbeli ajana karşı şansın olduğunu mu düşünüyorsun?
Peacock Slasher!
Tavus Kesici!
Take this!
Alın bunu!
Lethal Exploding Star!
Ölümcül Patlayan Yıldız!
Bull's-eye!
Tam isabet!
Nice updraft!
İyi patlamaydı!
Nose Fancy Cannon!
Süslü Sümük Topu!
Pitiful man!
Zavallı şey!
Usopp!
Usopp!
10,000 Kilo Press!
10.000 Kiloluk Baskı!
Give it a rest!
Kes şunu artık!
Why so agitated?
Niye bu kadar tedirginsin?
We're not gonna kill you just yet.
Seni henüz öldürmeyeceğiz.
We only came to capture you.
Şimdilik canlı lazımsın.
All per Mr. 3's orders.
Bay 3'ün emirleri doğrultusunda.
Mr. 3?!
Bay 3 mü?
The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
Mum gücüne sahip adam mı?!
He's on this island?!
Bu adada mı?!
That's right.
Aynen öyle.
He's a candle man who controls wax secreted from his body.
Bedeninden mum salgılayıp onu kontrol eden bir adam o!
You wretch!
Seni alçak!
What is all this?!
Bu da ne?
Isn't it obvious?
Görmüyor musun?
This is why I can't stand unsophisticated dolts.
İşte bu yüzden cahil dangalaklara katlanamıyorum.
I'm creating a work of art, obviously.
Elbette ki bir sanat eseri ortaya koyuyorum.
Just be a good little girl.
Uslu bir kız ol artık.
Did you honestly think you could escape from Baroque Works?
Gerçekten Baroque Works'tan kaçabileceğine inandın mı?
Even that guy with the bounty of 30 million was no match for us.
30 milyonluk kellesi olan o adam bile bizim dengimiz değil.
I can finally return the favor for Whisky Peak.
Whisky Peak'te yaptığının acısını nihayet senden çıkardım!
You wannabe pirates had it coming
Kendinizi korsan sanan sizler,
for sticking your noses into such a sensitive operation.
bu işe burnunuzu sokarak kendi sonunuzu getirdiniz.
We've already captured your swordsman friend and the other girl.
Kılıç ustası arkadaşını ve diğer kızı zaten yakaladık.
You caught Zoro?
Zoro'yu yakaladınız mı?
Huh?
Ha?
Then you guys are dead meat!
Öyleyse hapı yutmuşsunuz.
Oh?
Oh?
You talk awfully big...
Tatminkâr Bombamı...
for a guy who received one of my Kicky Bombs to the face.
yüzüne yemene rağmen hâlâ konuşabiliyorsun.
Those don't hurt one bit!
Biraz bile acıtmadı!
I'm gonna kick all your asses!
Seni mahvedeceğim!
Pitiful.
Zavallı şey.
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Die!
Geber!
Chump!
Aptal!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy-san! Luffy-san!
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Gidelim, Bayan Valentine!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Usopp! Karoo!
Usopp-san! Karoo!
Damn you!
Seni ifrit!
Give it up! Give it up!
Pes et gitsin!
Once solidified, my candle jacket is as hard as steel!
Mum örtüm katılaşınca çelikten farksız olur!
You giants may have brutish strength,
Devlerin sınırsız gücü...
but you're weak when compared to these bonds.
zaptedildiğinde hiçbir şey ifade etmez.
Brainpower wins out in the end.
Eninde sonunda akıl üstün gelir.
I won't stoop to needlessly face you head-on.
Gereksiz yere yüz yüze gelmekten kaçınırım.
Upon tasting victory, you lowered your guard,
Zaferin tadına varınca gardını düşürdün,
Brogy the Red Ogre.
Kızıl Dev Brogy.
Don't glare at me like that.
Bana öyle bakma.
You're so terrifying!
Korkudan dilim tutuldu!
You should be thrilled!
Mutlu olmalısın!
The duel has finally arrived at its long-awaited end.
Düellon sonunda sonuca erdi.
Didn't you fight for a whole century with your so-called pride on the line?
Bir asır boyunca şerefin için savaşmadın mı?
Shouldn't the taste of victory be especially sweet, then?
Bu durumda zaferin tadı muhteşem olmaz mı?
Even if the fruit is borne of another's assistance?
Bu kez dışarıdan bir yardım gelmiş olsa bile?
Do you disagree?
Yanılıyor muyum?
You didn't...!
Seni köpek!
But indeed!
Ama sonunda...
The final victory belongs to me!
gerçek galip benim!
Were you aware that your massive, long-standing bounties
Uzun zaman önce kafanıza konan ödülün,
amounted to 200 million berries?
o büyük miktardaki paranın...
Today, that is still the case.
hâlâ geçerli olduğunu biliyor muydun?
You scum!
Seni şeytan!
I feel as if I've stumbled upon a long-lost treasure!
Gömülü bir hazine keşfetmiş gibiyim.
So that's what you're after, huh?!
Demek bunun peşindesin ha?!
Hmm?
Hım?
Mr. 3!
Bay 3!
Here she is.
Onu getirdik.
Our company's little traitor.
Örgütümüzün haini.
What took so long?
Çok yavaşsınız.
I was getting sick of waiting.
Beklemekten sıkıldım.
Your underhanded scheme went too far, Mr. 3!
Kurnaz planların haddini aştı, Bay 3!
You arranged for Dorry's alcohol to explode!
Dorry'nin patlayan içkisini sen ayarladın!
What?!
Ne?!
Alcohol?
İçki mi?
The drink I gave to him... That alcohol?!
Ona verdiğim içki mi?!
Dorry!
Dorry!
How was your drink?! Hit the spot, didn't it?!
İçkin nasıldı?! İyi geldi ama değil mi?!
Yeah.
Evet.
Truly the nectar of the gods.
İlahi bir tadı vardı.
So, that's what you meant, Dorry?!
Demek bunu kastettin, Dorry?!
Wretched girl, giving away company secrets.
Yani zavallı kız, küçük numaramı anlamış.
Not that it matters.
Önemi yok.
You're helpless now, after all.
Ne de olsa artık çaresizsin.
Candle...
Mum...
Lock!
Kilidi!
Mr. 5!
Bay 5!
Huh?
Ha?
Bring the swordsman and the girl!
Kılıç ustasını ve kızı getirin.
Let us commence.
Başlayalım.
Extra-Large Candle Set!
Ekstra Özel Şamdan!
What's going on?!
Ne oluyor?!
Here they are.
İşte geri kalanlar.
Disgraceful.
Reziller.
Getting bested by these lowlifes was beyond embarrassing.
Bu adi heriflere yenilmek utanç vericiliğin de ötesindeydi.
I'm disgusted with myself.
Kendimden tiksiniyorum.
What is that?!
Bu da ne böyle?!
Nami... Mr. Bushido...
Nami-san... Bay Bushido...
Vivi!
Vivi!
What happened?! Weren't you with Luffy?!
Ne oldu?! Luffy'yle birlikte değil miydin?!
Yes, I was, but–
Evet ama–
If you mean Straw Hat, I took him out myself!
Hasır Şapka'yı kastediyorsan, işini bitirdim.
And I didn't even break a sweat.
Kolay bir işti.
You?
Sen mi?
Welcome, one and all, to my service set!
Hepiniz servis setime hoş geldiniz!
Is this how it feels to be a candle stuck in a cake?
Pastanın içine sıkışmış bir mum olmak böyle bir his mi?
What's that spinning thing up there?
Orada dönüp duran şey de ne?
And I can't move my legs.
Bacaklarım kıpırdamıyor bile.
Makes sense for them to keep us immobilized.
Bizi kıpırdayamaz hâlde tutmaları normal.
They're the enemy.
Ne de olsa düşmanız.
Too hard.
Çok sert.
And I can't get a solid hit on it from this stance.
Üstelik bu pozisyonda gücümü hiç kullanamıyorum.
Huh?! Something's raining down!
Bir şeyler yağıyor!
I hope you enjoy my candle service!
Özel şamdanımın keyfini çıkarın!
The wax particles settling down on you
Kafalarınıza damlayan mumla kaplı buğu...
will soon transform you into wax sculptures!
yakında sizi bal mumu figürlerine dönüştürecek!
You'll become perfect models of humankind,
Yeteneklerimle dahi gerçekleştiremeyeceğim...
such that my skills alone could not achieve!
mükemmel insan figürleri olacaksınız!
Your wax figures will have literally captured your spirit!
Yakında ruh içeren bal mumu figürleri olacaksınız.
Now, in the name of art...
Şimdi sanat için...
perish.
ölün.
Screw that!
Siktir git!
Why do we have to become your works of art?!
Niye senin sanat eserin olmak zorundayız?!
Brogy! Get back up and crush these maniacs!
Brogy-san! Orada öylece yatma!
You'll turn into a wax statue too, you know!
Bir şey yap, yoksa sen de bal mumu figürü olacaksın!
Man, that's a huge person.
Yuh, amma da iri kıyım biriymiş.
Nothing you say will move him to action!
Söylediğin hiçbir şey onu harekete geçiremez!
Despite a proud victory, he's realized the absurdity of his tears of joy.
Rakibinin yaralarını fark etmeden 100 yıldır dövüştüğü dostu Dorry'i,
He slew his friend Dorry, with whom he fought for 100 years,
kendi elleriyle öldürdüğünü daha yeni öğrendi.
but he utterly failed to notice the injuries Dorry had already sustained!
Üstelik ahmak, sevinç gözyaşlarının ne kadar boş olduğunu anladı.
Or, perhaps, were you actually mourning your dear friend?
Ya da belki, sevgili dostunu kaybedişine ağlıyordun?
Whatever the case, there's no turning back the hands of time, you fool!
Ne olursa olsun, zamanı geri alamazsın, budala!
I knew...
Biliyordum.
Huh?
Ha?
I knew about it.
Bir şeylerin ters gittiğini biliyordum.
From the moment we resumed our duel,
Dövüşümüze başladığımız andan itibaren...
I knew Dorry was hiding something.
Dorry'nin bir şey gizlediğini biliyordum.
Oh? You knew, huh?
Oh? Biliyordun ha?
A likely story!
Yalancı!
If so, then why didn't you call off the duel?
Öyleyse niye dövüşmeye devam ettin?
Anyone could see there was no restraint in your killing blow!
Ne kadar sert dövüştüğünü gördüm. Zerre kadar acıman yoktu!
A coward who knows nothing of the valor of battle...
Düellonun önemini anlamayan bir çocuğun...
would never understand the truth behind my tears!
gözyaşlarımın sebebini anlaması mümkün değil!
And how could you know?!
Sen ne anlarsın ki?
Are you suggesting that I dishonor a warrior who hides his injuries
Yaralarını saklayıp yine de dövüşen bir savaşçıyı...
and does battle anyway?!
küçük mü düşürseydim?!
A wounded warrior who chooses to keep fighting asks not for mercy!
Yaralı bir savaşçı dövüşmeye devam etmeyi seçtiğinde merhamet dilemez!
And now, I know the reason behind it.
Ve şimdi sebebini öğrendim.
With that knowledge, I will settle this using my own two hands!
Artık bildiğime göre, bu işi kendi ellerimle çözeceğim!
That's the very least I can do...
Değerli dostum Dorry'yi...
to honor my dear friend Dorry!
en azından bu şekilde onurlandırabilirim!
Brogy!
Brogy-san!
– Brogy!
– Brogy-san!
What an annoying, talkative monster.
Ne sinir bozucu, geveze bir canavar.
U... Usopp...
U... Usopp...
Usopp...!
Usopp...!
You gonna let them... get away with this?
Bu... onların yanına kâr mı kalacak?
No...
Hayır...
I won't.
Asla.
Are you... angry too?
Sen de mi... kızgınsın?
Alright! Let's all three of us...
Pekâlâ! Hadi şunları...
go kick their asses!
öldüresiye dövmeye gidelim!
Brogy!
Brogy-san!
What a halfwit!
Aptal!
I underestimated the brutish strength of these giants!
Devlerin acımasız gücünü hafife aldım!
It's clear now that simply restraining you won't be enough!
Görünen o ki seni daha iyi zapt etmeliyim!
Wax-Wax Arts: Handcuffs!
Mum Sanatı: Kelepçeler!
I'm just getting started!
Daha bitirmedim!
And now for the pièce de résistance!
Ve son dokunuş!
Take this!
Al!
Just try to move now, will you?!
Şimdi kurtul da göreyim!
How can he be so cruel?
Nasıl bu kadar acımasız olabilir?
And now, accelerate, candle service!
Şimdi hızlan, özel şamdanım!
Turn these people into wax figures!
Onları bal mumu figürlerine çevir!
M-My chest is starting to burn.
G-Göğsüm yanmaya başladı.
The wax mist is getting into our lungs!
Mum ciğerlerimize doluyor!
At this rate, we'll turn into wax statues from the inside out!
Bu gidişle içten dışa doğru bal mumu figürlerine dönüşeceğiz!
Yes! Yes!
Evet! Evet!
The more pained you look, the better!
Acı içinde görünmeniz her şeyi daha da güzelleştiriyor!
Expressions of pain and agony are the very things I seek in art!
Sanatta en değer verdiğim şey, acı ve elem dolu suratlardır!
Solidify while filled with terror!
Dehşet içindeyken katılaşın!
You call this art, you creepy topknot freak?!
Bu mu sanat, seni topuz kafalı ucube?!
And how dare you do that to Brogy!
Ve bunu Brogy-san'a yapmaya nasıl cüret edersin?!
This'll come back to bite you in the ass! You hear?!
Hak ettiğini bulacaksın! Duyuyor musun?!
Scream and shout as much as you want!
İstediğin kadar bağır!
For 100 years...
100 yıl...
day in and day out, we fought and fought.
Günbegün, dövüş üstüne dövüş...
We dueled to maintain our pride as warriors of Elbaph!
Elbaf savaşçıları olarak şerefimiz üzerine düelloya tutuştuk!
So then,
Ama bize...
how is this what you promised, Elbaph, god of war?!
bu sonu mu layık gördün, savaş tanrısı Elbaf?!
If this is how we are to meet our end, Elbaph,
Böyle zavallı bir son yerine daha iyisini haketmiyor muyuz, Elbaf?!
Should we not die in battle?!
Savaşarak ölmemiz gerekmez miydi?!
What a splendid expression!
Ne muhteşem bir ifade!
Yes! That sorrow! That grief! That struggle!
İşte bu! Acı! Keder! Istırap!
What a marvelous work of art!
Ne harika bir sanat eseri!
Elbaph!
Elbaf!
Oh no! My hands won't move!
Olamaz! Ellerim kıpırdamıyor!
I don't wanna die this way! Can't we do something?!
Böyle bitmesin! Bir şeyler yapamaz mıyız?!
My body's already becoming stiff!
Bedenim çoktan sertleşmeye başladı!
What do we do?!
Ne yapabiliriz?!
Z-Zoro! Do something!
Z-Zoro! Bir şeyler düşün!
Hey, old-timer.
Hey, ihtiyar.
You can still move, can't you?
Hâlâ biraz gücün var, değil mi?
Huh?
Ha?
So can I.
Benim de.
How about you and I... crush these guys?
Şunları birlikte ezmeye ne dersiniz?
Hold on, Zoro! What are you doing?!
Bekle, Zoro! Ne yapıyorsun?!
You're not seriously–
Yoksa–
Yeah.
Evet.
Don't joke about cutting off your legs!
Bacaklarını kesme konusunda şaka yapma!
It's not a joke.
Şaka değil.
It's the only way outta here.
Buradan çıkmamızın tek yolu bu.
And you two?
Kararınız nedir?
What about us?! It's futile!
Kararımız mı? Mümkün değil!
Even if you escape, they'll just catch you again!
Aşağı inmeyi başarsak bile yine yakalanacağız!
There's no way to know that unless we try!
Denemeden bilemeyiz!
After all, we're gonna kick the bucket if we stay here.
Zaten burada kalırsak nalları dikeceğiz.
Instead, let's put up one hell of a struggle!
Bari destansı bir direniş sergileyelim!
I'm not gonna lie down and die for this scum!
Bu değersiz böceklere karşı bu kadar kolay ölemem!
Right?!
Haksız mıyım?
What the hell? Is he crazy?
Neden bahsediyor bu? Delirmiş mi?
A mere bluff!
Blöf yapıyorsun!
What he's threatening to do is ludicrous!
Yapmakla tehdit ettiğin şey çok gülünç!
It's all an act!
Rol yapıyorsun!
You're pretty cocky, kiddo.
Ne korkusuz bir çocuk.
How embarrassing.
Ben ise acınacak hâldeyim.
I had just about lost the will to fight.
Mücadele kararlılığımı yitirmek üzereydim.
But your fiery spirit has me raring to go!
Ama içindeki tutku, beni savaşmaya heveslendirdi!
You can't be serious, right?!
Ciddi olamazsın, değil mi?!
How will you fight once you're free?!
Bacakların olmadan nasıl dövüşeceksin?
Who knows?
Kim bilir?
But...
Ama...
I plan to win.
kazanmayı planlıyorum.
What's with these guys?!
Bu herifin nesi var?!
They're off their rockers!
Kafayı yemiş!
What kind of man is he?!
Böyle bir adam nasıl var olabilir?!
Still, I've seen this look somewhere before...
Ama o gözleri daha önce bir yerde görmüşüm gibi.
Princess Vivi!
Prenses Vivi!
Are you resolved to stay alive?
Hayatta kalmaya kararlı mısın?
W-Wait!
B-Bekle!
I'll fight, too!
Ben de dövüşeceğim!
Vivi!
Vivi!
Good to hear.
Bunu duymak güzel.
Let's do it, kiddo!
Başlıyoruz, çocuk!
Ridiculous! Do you even have a plan of attack?!
Aptalca! Bir saldırı stratejin var mı acaba?!
Hey, you guys!
Ulan!
Get ready to get your asses kicked!
Dayak yemeye hazır olun!
What?
Ne?
Let's do it, Usopp!
Hadi yapalım, Usopp!
Yeah!
Evet!
Bird?!
Kuş?!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Usopp!
Usopp!
Karoo!
Karoo!
Master Brogy! Your anger is now our own!
Usta Brogy! Öfkeni devralıyoruz!
Usopp...!
Usopp...!
Beat those guys beyond recognition
Şunları eşek sudan gelinceye dek pataklayıp...
and send them flying far away from here!
dünyanın öteki ucuna fırlatın!
Yeah! I will!
Evet! Yapacağız!
They spoiled the duel the old giant guys were having!
İhtiyar devlerin düellosunu mahvettiler!
Do you really have the highest bounty in the East Blue?
Cidden Doğu Mavi'nin en yüksek ödülüne mi sahipsin?
My, how Marine Headquarters' standards have fallen!
Denizciler, kesinlikle standartlarını düşürmüş!
Whoa! That hair is weird!
Yuh! Tuhaf bir kafan var!
Shut your mouth!
Kapa' çeneni!
It's a burning number three!
Yanan bir üç numara!
Shut it!
Sus!
Break this pillar first, Luffy!
Önce şu sütunu kır, Luffy!
We're about to turn into wax figures!
Bal mumu figürleri olmak üzereyiz!
Huh?
Ha?
Oh? You're in trouble?
Ne? Başınız dertte mi?
Nope. No trouble here.
Hayır, önemli bir şey değil.
Hey, wait! Your legs!
Hey, dur! Bacakların!
Yeah.
Evet.
I got about halfway through them, I'd say.
Sadece yarısına kadar kestim.
How can you say that's "no trouble"?!
Nasıl "önemli bir şey değil" dersin?!
Like she said, could you bust this pillar for us, Luffy?
Her neyse Luffy, önce şu sütunu kırabilir misin?
After that, go wild.
Sonra yardırırsın.
Yeah, sure thing!
Elbette!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Ben o kadar emin olmazdım.
I don't know what it is, but we're gonna break it!
Ne olduğunu bilmiyorum ama önce onu kıracağız!
Oh, yeah!
Tamam!
Got it!
Anladım!
I'm not the same man as before!
Yenilenmiş gibi hissediyorum!
Hurry before we turn solid!
Biz katılaşmadan önce acele edin!